Preliminary Guide to the AIDS Action Foundation records, 1984-2006 MS2212
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Other AIDS organizations, 1998-2005, many undated; Series 9; 4.5 Linear Feet
  - CAEAR Cities Advocating Emergency AIDS Relief, undated; Series 9 (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - Campaign for Fairness, undated; Series 9 (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - CBC heathcare access rally [Congressional Black Caucus], 2003; Series 9 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - CBC panel 2 [Congressional Black Caucus], 2002 September 12; Series 9 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Congressional Black Caucus issues forum, 2001 September; Series 9 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - CDC Campaign, 2001; Series 9 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Centennial Area Health, undated; Series 9 (Box 48, Folder 22)
  - Central VA AIDS Service, undated; Series 9 (Box 48, Folder 23)
  - CFC, undated; Series 9 (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - CHAC Info [CDC/HRSA Advisory Committee on HIV and STD Prevention and Treatment], 2005; Series 9 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Colorado AIDS etc, undated; Series 9 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Columbia School of Public Health NY, undated; Series 9 (Box 48, Folder 25)
  - CPR [Coalition to Protect Research], 2004-2005; Series 9 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - ETHA [Early Treatment of HIV Act], 2003; Series 9 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - ETHA [Early Treatment of HIV Act], 2001-2002; Series 9 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - MATEC [National Minority AIDS Training and Education Centers], undated; Series 9 (Box 49, Folder 16)
  - Sample letters, undated; Series 9 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - The Cross-Over Ministry, undated; Series 9 (Box 48, Folder 26)
  - UMD New Jersey, undated; Series 9 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - FAPP [Federal AIDS Policy Partnership], 2004-2005; Series 9 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Ryan White Care Act
  - Department of Health and Human Services, undated; Series 9 (Box 48, Folder 31)
  - FASA, undated; Series 9 (Box 61, Folder 18)
  - Florida Academy of Family Physicians, undated; Series 9 (Box 48, Folder 27)
  - Florida AIDS Education, undated; Series 9 (Box 48, Folder 29)
  - Friends of CDC / HRSA APHA, 2004; Series 9 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Global international focus group findings, 2000 June; Series 9 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Health and Human Services, 2004-2005; Series 9 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - HAAC Testimony (Jeff) [HRSA AIDS Advisory Committee], 1998 December 4; Series 9 (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Health Action News, undated; Series 9 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Hill Briefing Labor and Health, undated; Series 9 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Hispanic CBO Campaign [Congressional Budget Office], undated; Series 9 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Infectious Disease Physicians, undated; Series 9 (Box 48, Folder 33)
  - Letter Labor and Health and Human Services for testifying, 1999; Series 9 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - State of Florida Dept. of Health and Rehab. Services, undated; Series 9 (Box 48, Folder 28)
  - University of Hawaii, undated; Series 9 (Box 48, Folder 30)
  - University of Illinois, undated; Series 9 (Box 48, Folder 32)
  - Johns Hopkins University, undated; Series 9 (Box 48, Folder 34)
  - Kansas City AIDS Research, undated; Series 9 (Box 48, Folder 35)
  - Kapiolani Medical Center for Women and Children, undated; Series 9 (Box 48, Folder 36)
  - University of Mass Medical Center, undated; Series 9 (Box 48, Folder 37)
  - NASTAD position paper [National Alliance of State and Territorial AIDS Directors], undated; Series 9 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - NASTAD [National Alliance of State and Territorial AIDS Directors], undated; Series 9 (Box 68, Folder 8)
  - NMAETC [National Minority AIDS Training and Education Centers], 2003; Series 9 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Northwest AIDS Foundation, undated; Series 9 (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - Presidential Advisory Council on HIV and AIDS PACHA, 2002; Series 9 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - PACHA meeting [Presidential Advisory Council on HIV and AIDS], 2002 June 21-22; Series 9 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - PACHA notes [Presidential Advisory Council on HIV and AIDS], undated; Series 9 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - PEPFAR [President's Emergency Plan for AIDS Relief], 2004; Series 9 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Ryan White Working Group, 2005-2006; Series 9 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - SAC [Southern AIDS Coalition], 2005; Series 9 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - San Francisco AIDS Foundation, 1995; Series 9 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - SCALE Conference [Stakeholders Consultation To Achieve Linkages and Engagement], 2004 November 16; Series 9 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Southern AIDS Coalition, 2004; Series 9 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Southern California AIDS Education, undated; Series 9 (Box 48, Folder 20)
  - Strength for Caring, 2002 October 25-27; Series 9 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - University of CA San Francisco, undated; Series 9 (Box 48, Folder 21)
  - University of Colorado, undated; Series 9 (Box 48, Folder 24)
  - UCHAPS [Urban Coalition for HIV/AIDS Prevention Services], 2003; Series 9 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - USCA Contacts [United Conference on AIDS], 2002; Series 9 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - USCA [United Conference on AIDS], 2002; Series 9 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - USCA workshops, roundtables, and seminars [United Conference on AIDS], 2003; Series 9 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - University Lobbyist, undated; Series 9 (Box 49, Folder 3)